OLANIPEKUN FASILAT ADEOLA

26, Olawore Estate Atanoba, Offa, Kwara State. **E-mail:** olanipekunfasilat1991@gmail.com **Tel:** 08136797782, 09122903446.

PERSONAL DETAILS

State of Origin: Kwara State

Marital Status:

L.G.A:
Offa
Nationality:
Nigerian
Religion:
Islam
Gender:
Female

CAREER OBJECTIVES

To become a notable customer service delivery expert by deploying my very sturdy passion for good customer service delivery and consumer insights, its impacts and relevance across various business environments regardless of sector, industry or geography.

EDUCATION

Federal University of Ilorin, Kwara State	2015-2021
Federal Polytechnic Offa, Kwara State	2012-2015
Offa Grammar School, Offa, Kwara State	2004-2010
Adeola Model School, Offa, Kwara State	1998-2004

CERTIFICATE OBTAINED

National Youth Service Corp (NYSC)	September, 2022
BSc Quantity Surveying (2nd Class Honours, Lower Division)	August, 2021
National Diploma in Estate Management (Lower Credit)	December, 2015
National Business & Technical Examination Board (NABTEB)	June 2011
West African Senior School Certificate (WASSC)	June, 2014

WORK EXPERIENCE

National Youth Service 2021-2022

Fortunate Foundation College, 7, Atele Street, Behind World Oil Filling Station, Lagos-Ibadan Expressway, Oyo State.

Position: Teacher

Responsibilities

- Tutoring Senior Students
- Organizing, Coordinating and Anchoring School Debates Competitions
- Time Keeping Management

Industrial Training

2019 - 2019

Lylius Integrated Resources Limited:

Behind Evergreen Schools, Asa-Dam, Ilorin Kwara State

Position: Industrial Trainee

Project Executed

Proposed Multipurpose Auditorium, Armti, Kwara State	Mar. 2019-Aug. 2019
Rehabilitation of Oke-Oyi/Oloru Road, Kwara State	May 2019-Aug. 2019
Rehabilitation of Omu-Aran/Ajase Road, Kwara State	Aug. 2019-Dec. 2019
Residential Development, Coca-Cola Road, Ilorin, Kwara State	Aug. 2019- Dec. 2019
Proposed Lylius Hotels, Asa Dam Road, Ilorin, Kwara State	Sept. 2019-Dec. 2019

Responsibilities

Site Supervision of works

Site measurement and valuation of executed works

Preparation of tender document and prequalification of contracts

Preparation of Bills of Quantities

Site meetings

Preparation of progress reports

SIWES 2017-2017

Lylius Integrated Resources Limited

Behind Evergreen Schools, Asa-Dam, Ilorin Kwara State

Position: Industrial Trainee

Project Executed

Proposed Renovation of Ilorin Residence, Ilorin, Kwara State	July. 2017- Oct. 2017
Residential Development, Flower Garden, Ilorin	July. 2017- Oct. 2017

Responsibilities

- Site Supervision of works
- Site measurement and valuation of executed works
- Preparation of tender document and prequalification of contracts
- Preparation of Bills of Quantities
- Preparation of progress reports

LEARDERSHIP SKILLS

Interpersonal skills

Working with minimum or no supervision

Ability to work under pressure

Ability to manage others

Quick at learning new skills and software

Critical thinking and analytical

HOBBIES

Reading, listening to Music, Meeting People and Sharing Ideas,

REFEREES

Dr. Yusuf Amuda

Senior Lecturer
Department of Quantity Surveying
Faculty of Environmental Science
University of Ilorin *Tel:* 0803 450 7354

Mr. Ademola Oyewumi

Principal Partner Chartered Professionals Ltd 5, Vori Close, Ogba, Lagos.